Guide to the Howard Seifert Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Howard Seifert papers
1960-1977
SC0173
Seifert, Howard, 1911-1977
Seifert,, 1911-1977.
39.5 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Mrs. Howard Seifert, 1977, and administrative transfer, Department of Aeronautics and Astronautics, 1979.
Information about Access
None.
Biography
Howard Seifert, an authority on rocket propulsion of space vehicles, was professor of aeronautics and astronautics at Stanford from 1960 to 1976. He also directed the Physical Sciences Laboratory at the United Aircraft Corporation (1960-65) and was president of the American Rocket Society (1960). Before joining the Stanford faculty, he was on the staff at the Jet Propulsion Laboratory and Space Technology Laboratories and a visiting professor at UCLA.
Scope and Content
Papers include correspondence, photographs, newsclippings, notes, memoranda, reports, reprints, proposals, and class materials (notes, problems, exams, and reference sources). Some materials pertain to his work with the Jet Propulsion Laboratory and NASA.
Access Terms
Jet Propulsion Laboratory (U.S.).; Seifert, Howard,, 1911-1977.; Stanford University. Department of Aeronautics and Astronautics. -- General subdivision--Faculty.;; United States.. National Aeronautics and Space Administration..; Aeronautics--Research.; Clippings.; Photoprints.; Rocketry.; Solar energy--Research.
Collection Contents
- General Files, Part 1
  - Miscellaneous unfoldered materials (Box 1)
    - Journal - Trip to Arabia and technical notes for trip (University of Petroleum and Minerals, Dhammam, Saudi Arabia), (2/21/77)
    - Brochures: University of Petroleum and Minerals and assorted energy topics
    - Photos: Luna Colloquim at STL, (1959)
    - Clippings: Desalination, (2/20/77)
    - Arabia trip itinerary and consulting agreements (University of Petroleum and Minerals), visa applications, local information, etc.
    - University of Petroleum and Minerals planning handbook, map, memos, history, project proposals
    - Notes, (1/2/77)
    - Assorted photos
    - Research report Electrical Breakdown Between Cylinders in Vacuum by Seifert
  - KLS: doc., moving, wedding (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Personal Stanford history (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - News clippings (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Notes, clippings, brochures (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Microprojector (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Research plans (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letters (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photos (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letters (to and from children) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cyl. lens theory (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Property (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Misc. notes, recital announcement (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Eyes - double vision, musical activities (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Clippings about Prof. Seifert and Wyld Propulsion award (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Insurance policies (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Memo - disposal of property after death (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Hopping Transporters for Lunar Exploration.", (8/69) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Laser Doppler Technique for the Measurement of Particle Velocity.", (1967) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Laser-Doppler Particle Sensor for Rocket Exhausts.", (3/69) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Laser-Doppler Technique for Measurement of Particle Velocity in Gas-PArticle Two-Phase Flow.", (6/66) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rocket Propulsion, (7/68) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Non-Chemical Propulsion, (1968) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - State of Propulsion Art, (7/68) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - AGARD Combustion and Propulsion Panel, (1962) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "A Miniature Kundt Tube.", (12/39) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Shocks Induced by Secondary Fluid Injection.", (1/64) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Lunar Pogo Stick.", (6/67) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - La Scuola in Azione, (1962-63) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Student receipts (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bibliography on Space Travel and Rockets (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sohn Orbit Computer (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Book and UCLA: brochures and covers (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "Propulsion for Space Vehicles.", (1962) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Student receipts, (1962) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "Stop-Light Dilemna", (3/62) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "Studies of Unstable Combustion in Solid Propellant Rocked Engines", (3/62) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "Can We Decrease Our Entropy?", (6/61) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Book of Knowledge Article, (1960) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Turbopumps for Small Rocket Engines, (9/57) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Thrust Coefficient and Expansion Ratio Tables, (2/56) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Notification of Acceptance of Paper for Symposium on Ballistic Missiles, (6/56) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Modern Physics for the Engineer, (8/55) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Development of the Guided Missile, (9/55) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Twenty-Five Years of Rocket Development, (10/55) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Semantics Bibliography, (1953) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Variable Propellant Density, (6/53) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Review Conquest of the Moon, (12/53) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Inventions of Importance to Aviation, (8/53) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Compressible Flow, (1953) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Listing of Reports, Pre-1953 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Comparison of Adiabatic and Isothermal Expansion Processes in Rocket Nozzles, (6/52) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - The Effect of Variable Propellant Density on Rocket Performance, (8/52) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Friction Tape Produces Glow Discharge, (9/52) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Letter to the Editor - American Journal of Physics, (9/52) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - The Jet Propulsion Laboratory, (10/52) (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Corporal Missile School, (1951) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Heat-Transfer Studies Relating to Rocket Power-Plant Development, (1951) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Make Your Own Microprojector, (1/51) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - The Scientific Monthly (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Central Data-Recording System for A Jet-Propulsion Laboratory, (10/51) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Aircraft Instrumentation and Control Course, (1950) (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Rocket Propulsion Elements and Rocket Guns and Targets, (2/49) (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Is the Nuclear-Powered Rocket Feasible?, (5/49) (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Compressibility Effects in Two Phase Flow, (7/49) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Stream Paths from Rotating Liquid Propellant Injectors, (9/48) (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Problems in the Application of Nuclear Energy to Rocket Propulsion, (1/47) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - The Physics of Rockets, (1/47) (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Physics of Rockets: Liquid Propellant Rockets, (4/47) (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Physics of Rockets: Dynamics of Long-Range Rockets, (6/47) (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Cal Tech Research Topics for Thesis and Assorted Memos, (1947) (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Jet Propulsion - Its Effect Upon Engineering Education, (10/46) (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Program for Pasadena Meeting of the American Physical Society, (12/44) (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - JPL Report - Development of Regeneratively-Cooled Liquid Propellant Jet Motors, (7/43) (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Electrical Breakdown in Vacuum Between Electrodes of Large Area, (6/42) (Box 2A, Folder 58)
  - Detection of Flaws in Metal Coatings, (6/42) (Box 2A, Folder 59)
  - The Induction Inverter, (9/42) (Box 2A, Folder 60)
  - Editorial for 1/12/60 issue of Astronautics (Box 2A, Folder 61)
  - List of Publications: (Box 2A, Folder 62)
    Shocks Induced by Secondary Fluid Injection (1/64)
    Use of Preformed Solid Particles in Colloidal Propulsion (9/67)
  - Propulsion Dynamics of Lunar Hoppers, (12/74) (Box 2A, Folder 63)
  - Space Mission Slide Chart; Pocket Planetarium; Rocket Thrust Computer; Scientific Catalog; and Portable Flight Path Model Photos (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Space Vehicle Designer; Pocket Planetarium; and Rocket Thrust Computers (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pocket Planetarium Design (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Induction Inverter and "Vapor Discharge Cavity Oscilloscope", (9/42); (8/42) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Student Projects in Physics at Kalamazoo College, (6/40) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Electrical Breakdown Between Cylinders in Vacuum plus Notes, (1942) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Transmission and Reflection of Plastics and Metal Blocks in the Far Infra-Red, (11/40) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - A Miniature Kundt Tube, (12/39) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, (1964) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Induction Inverter, (9/42) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - BS, MS, PhD Theses (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Survey of Electrically-Powered Rockets, (1963) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Stop-Light Dilemma and Correspondence, (3/62) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Notes on Talk about Lunar Hopper (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - TV Script for Show about JPL; Notes: The Scientist's Code of Ethics Notes: Application of Electrical Analog Computers to Rocket Propulsion and Index of Visits to British Establishments, (4/52); (10/51); (1945) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - (Binder) Talks, 1960-70 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - (Binder) Talks, 8/55-6/60 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - (Binder) FORTRAN IV Notes (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - (Loose) FORTRAN Class Notes (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - FORTRAN IV Book (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - WATFIV Compiler Guide, (8/70) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Introduction to Programming Concepts (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - BASIC User's Manual, (7/70) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - BASIC User's Guide to Remote Terminals, (10/69) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Guide to the BALLOTS Files (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Lectures, Handouts, Etc. for EE 231 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Inactive Documents (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Journal of Spacecraft and Rockets article by HSS, (8/69); 2 copies, (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Space Technology covers (book edited by HSS), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - A Central Data-Recording System for a Jet Propulsion Laboratory, (1959) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Book Review by HSS: Rocket Power and Space Flight, (1/58) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - UCLA Space Technology Brochure, (1/58) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence regarding Thrust Coefficient and Expansion Ratio Tables, (1/59) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - The Performance of a Rocket with Tapered Exhaust velocity, (12/57) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - The Effect of Propellant Energy and Mass Distribution on Rocket Propulsion Efficiency, (1/57) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Turbopumps for Small Rocket Engines, (9/57) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - AA 280A Class Files
    - Ballistic Problems/Solutions (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Ballistics Solutions, (1/68) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Ballistics Solutions (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Nozzle Flow Problems (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Nozzle Flow Solutions (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Engine Design Problems, (1967) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Engine Design Solutions (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Thermochemistry 1-8 Problems (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Thermochemistry Solutions (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Heat Transfer Problems (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Heat Transfer Solutions (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Problems and Solutions 67-27, 28, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Problems and Solutions 67-12 through 67-16 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Solutions to Problem Set 69-3 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Problem 67-8 through 16, (1967) (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Problem 67-7, (6/30/67) (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 67-1 Tullig Solution (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Midterm Exam, (2/69) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 1969 Winter Final (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Thermochemistry Quiz, (2/20/70) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Hybrid Problem, (1969) (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Hybrid Rocket Design, (4/11/68) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Midterm Solutions, (2/69) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Thermochemistry A Quiz and Thermochemistry B Quiz, (2/24/69) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Thermochemistry A/B Quiz and Solutions, (2/26/69) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Thermochemistry Quiz and Solution, (2/23/68) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Summer 1968 Midterm (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Final Exam, (3/68) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Midterm Solutions, (2/68) (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Midterm Exam, (2/7/68) (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Handout Stage Mass Ratio Vs. Stage Velocity Increase, (1967) (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Propulsion Final, (8/18/67) (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Quiz Solutions, (1967) (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Thermochemistry Quiz, (2/27/67) (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Thermochemistry Quiz Solution, (2/27/67) (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Final Exam, (3/24/67) (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Assorted Problems (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Course Notes (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Stage Optimization Procedure (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Periodic Table of the Elements (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Gamma Curves (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Theoretical Performance of Rocket Propellant Combinations (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Background Data Form (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Winter Quarter Schedule, `69/'70 and `71/`72 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Summer Quarter Schedule, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Set I Rocket Fundamentals (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Set II Ballistics and Staging (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Set III Multi-Stage Rockets (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Set IV Satellite Motion (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Set V Rocket Thrust (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Set VI Design Parameters (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Set VII Simplified Liquid Rocket Design (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Set VIII Solid Propellant Rockets (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Set IX Solid Propellant Rocket Design (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Set X Thermochemistry of Rocket Propellants (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Set XI Heat Transfers in Chemical Rockets (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Set XII Ablation (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Set XIII Hybrid Rockets (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Class Grades and Schedules, Tau Beta Pi Survey Results (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Space Suttle Bulletins (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Combustion Processes in a Bipropellant Liquid Rocket Engine (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Reference and Source Material (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Reference: Satellite Auxiliary-Propulsion Selection Techniques (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Reference Materials (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Reference and Source Materials -, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Reference Material: Propulsion for Space Flight (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Reference Material: Nozzle Performance, One-Dimensional Theory (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Reference Material: Flow Equations, Impulse Expressions (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Reference Material: ME 237A Notes and Problems (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Reference Material: Mechanisms of Thermochemical Erosion (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Reference Material: General Ablation Data (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Reference Material: Effect of Chamber Pressure on Ablation Rate of a Packaged Liquid Thrust Chamber (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Reference Material: Methods to Determine Step Weights of Rockets to Minimize Initial Gross Weight (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Reference Material: Estimating Performance Capabilities of Boost Rockets (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Reference Material: Liquid Rocket Heat Transfer (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Reference Materials: Course Outlines (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Reference Materials: Status Report on Large Solid Booster Nozzle Inserts (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Reference Materials: Stage Optimization Curves (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Reference Materials: Bartz Heat Transfer Theory (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Reference Material: On Incremental Rockets (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Reference Material: Estimating Performance Capabilities of Boost Rockets (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Reference Material: Assorted Hybrids Reference (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Reference Material: Space Systems Propulsion Studies (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Reference Material: Ultra-High Temperature Chambers (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Reference Material: Rocket Power Concept (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Reference Material: The Problem of Escape from the Earth by Rocket (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Reference Material: Fundamental Principles of Reaction Propulsion (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Reference Material: Altman Enthalpy Tables (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Reference Material: Energy Limitations on Space Navigation (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Reference Notes: Liquid Propellant Rockets (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Reference Notes: Space Slide Rules (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - AA 280B Class Files
    - Ramjet Problem Set (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Air Augmented Rocket Problems (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Solutions to Air Augmented Rocket Problems, (5/10/71) (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Problem AAR-1 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Solutions: Two-Phase Flow (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Two-Phase Flow Problems, (4/70, 4/71) (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Thrust Vector Control Problems, (1969-71) (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - TVC Problem 1 Solutions (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Hybrid Rocket Problem H-1 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Solution to Hybrid Problem H-1, (4/71) (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Characteristics of a Good Solution (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Turbojet Problems (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Kaplan Problem (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Ramjet Problem (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Problem 67-10 Solution, (5/25/67) (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Hybrid Rocket Design, Problem 67-1, (4/13/67) (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Problem 69-5 Ramjet (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Solution 67-2 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Solution 67-2, (4/25/67) (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Solutions - Ramjet, (5/16/67) (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Ramjet Design Solutions, (5/16/68) (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Units Problem 69-3, (4/22/69) (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Ramjet Problem, (5/16/56) (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Problem 67-2 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Advanced Chemical Propulsion Spring 1972 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Advanced Propulsion (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Liquid-Solid Rockets (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Charts and Text Thrust Vector Control by Secondary Injection into Rocket Exhaust (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Charts and Text Liquid Rockets, (1969) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Charts and Text Liquid Rocket Charts, (1969) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Charts and Text Gasdynamic Structure of Jets from Plug Nozzles (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Charts and Graphs Typical Throttling/Performance Tradeoffs Without Aft-End Injection (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Charts and Text The Ramjet (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Charts and Text The Thermodynamics of Aircrafts Jet Engines (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Charts and Text Aft-End Injection (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Notes: Dynamics of Two-Phase Flow in Rocket Nozzles, (1968) (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Lecture Notes: Liquid Rockets, (1969) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Lecture Notes: Selected Bibliography on Transverse Jets to 1966 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Lecture Notes Hybrid Throttling, (6/12/67) (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Financial: EMPTY (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Lecture Notes Dynamics of Two-Phase Flow in Rocket Nozzles Spring, (1967) (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Lecture Notes Index to Two-Phase Flow Notes Based on UTC 2102FR (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Lecture Notes - Hybrid Figure Originals (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Class Grades and Schedules (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Advanced Chemical Propulsion Schedule for Spring 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Advanced Chemical Propulsion Schedules and Grades, (Spring 1968) (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Advanced Chemical Propulsion Schedules and Grades, (Spring 1967) (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Reusable Launch and Reentry Vehicles for Space Flight Short Course, (August 1969) (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Hybrid Experiment UTC (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Briefing to the Advanced Propulsion Comparison Steering Committee, (March 1, 1972) (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Reference and Source Materials: Miscellaneous Articles (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Reference Material: Internal Rocket Dynamics (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Reference Material: Hybrid Second Copy and Miscellaneous Notes (EMPTY) (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Study Calculations and Report "Air Breathers" (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Reference Material "Combustion - Eustis 1961" (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Reference Material: Misc. Articles from Various Companies Concerning Rockets, Engines and Thrust (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Reference Material: Development of the Post Injection Propulsion System for the Mariner C Spacecraft (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Reference Material: Rains - Feed System Notes 1958 and 1962 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Reference Material: J. Grey - Feed System 1961 (and Dupe) (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Reference Material: Hoffman Liquid Rocket Survey 1961 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Reference Material: Gas Storage in Tanks (French:, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Reference Material: Rocketdyne Propellant Charts, (1963) (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Reference Material: Rains TVC Charts 1963-64 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Reference Material: Student Design (Frewing, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Reference Material: Ross on Combustion Chambers Scaling, (1965) (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Reference Material: Glassman Liquid Notes (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Reference Material: Osborn, Matheson and Kruger: System Problems (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Reference Material: Miscellaneous Booste, Instability and Premix (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Reference and Source Material: Feed Systems 1960-61 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Two-Phase Flow (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - AA 283: Problem Sets, Quizzes, Notes (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - AA 283: Student Reports (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - AA 283: Things to File (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Hoffman: Calculation of the Lifting Force (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Stanford Propulsion Courses: Seifert A200 Lecture, (11/9/67) (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - A200: Rocket Propulsion (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - AA 283: Class Grades and Schedules (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - AA 283: Aircraft Propulsion Source Material (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - AA 200: Engine Analysis of Flight Vehicles (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Aerodynamics for Naval Aviators (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - NASA Report: Pressure Recovery Performance of Conical Diffusers at High Subsonic Mach Numbers (Box 6A, Folder 54)
  - NASA Report: An Investigation of Several BACA 1-Series Axisymmetric Inlets at Mach Numbers from 0.4 to 1.29 (Box 6A, Folder 55)
  - NASA Notes: Performance of an Asymmetric Short Annular Diffuser with a Non-Diverging Inner Wall Using Suction (Box 6A, Folder 56)
  - NASA Memorandum: Drag and Distribution Measurements of Single-Element Fuel Injectors for Supersonic Combustors (Box 6A, Folder 57)
  - GE Report: Subsonic and Supersonic Jets and Supersonic Suppressor Characteristics (Box 6A, Folder 58)
  - Aircraft Reprint: "Review of SCRAMJET Propulsion Technology" (Box 6A, Folder 59)
  - The Aircraft Gas Turbine Engine and Its Operation, (2 Copies) (Box 6A, Folder 60)
  - Allison 250 Series Gas Turbine Engines 317 to 400 Shaft HP for Light Helicopters and Fixed-Wing Aircraft (Box 6A, Folder 61)
  - Garrett-Airesearch TPE 331/T76 Turboprop Record (Box 6A, Folder 62)
  - Program Schedule, 1961-69; AA 298: (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - UTC Technical Seminars (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - JPL Research Topics Seperation in Nozzles, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - JPL Documents (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Mills-Summerfield Hassle, (January 1947) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Old Cal Tech Notes: Nozzle Flow Paper, (April 1958) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Old Cal Tech Notes: CIT Liquid Notes (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Old Cal Tech Notes: CIT Solid Notes (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Syllabi and Notes - Other Schools: Astro Propulsion - MIT, 1964 (Oates) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Astro Propulsion Notes MIT, (1964) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Syllabi and Notes - Other Schools: Rocket Exam - UCIA, 1957 (Levine) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Syllabi and Notes - Other Schools: UCIA - Answers to Sutton, 2nd Edition (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Syllabi and Notes - Other Schools: A Compilation of Lectures Given at Arnold Center as Part of the Work-Study Program, Summers of 1960 and 1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Syllabi and Notes - Other Schools: A Compilation of Lectures Given at Arnold Center as Part of the Work-Study Program, Supp., Summers of 1960 and 1961 (Box 7, Folder 13a)
  - NASA-SU Summer Institute, 1964-66 (Box 7, Folder 14)